True Spirit is a adventure, drama, history film directed by Sarah Spillane.
When the tenacious young sailor Jessica Watson sets out to be the youngest person to sail
solo, nonstop and unassisted around the world, many expect her to fail.
With the support of her sailing coach and mentor Ben Bryant and her parents, Jessica is determined to accomplish what was thought
to be impossible, navigating some of the world’s most challenging stretches of ocean over the course of 210 days.
Jessica Watson, played by Teagan Croft.
Ben Bryant, played by Cliff Curtis.
Young Jessica, played by Alyla Browne.
Roger Watson, played by Josh Lawson.
Julie Watson, played by Anna Paquin.
Emily Watson, played by Bridget Webb.
True Spirit is a 2023 Australian biographical drama film directed by Sarah
Spillane and written by Spillane, Cathy Randall, and Rebecca Banner.
The film is based on the 2010 memoir of the same name by
Jessica Watson, played by Teagan Croft.
She is an Australian sailor who was awarded the Order of Australia Medal and is on the Australian
Sailing Hall of Fame after attempting a solo global circumnavigation at the age of 16.
The film was made available for streaming on Netflix on 3 February 2023.
The tone is emotional.